<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nail Art on Nails Art and Hairstyles Ideas</title>
    <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/categories/nail-art/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nail Art on Nails Art and Hairstyles Ideas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright 2021 [hairpict.github.io/hair-nail](https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 08:50:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/categories/nail-art/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>15 Cute Acrylic nails for gold dress for Natural Beauty</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/acrylic-nails-for-gold-dress/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 08:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/acrylic-nails-for-gold-dress/</guid>
      <description>Acrylic Nails For Gold Dress, One nail is in solid gold. I recommend keeping your nails short and in a squarish oval shape squoval in order to keep your hands looking youthful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Top Acrylic nails thetford for Trend 2021</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/acrylic-nails-thetford/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 07:53:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/acrylic-nails-thetford/</guid>
      <description>Acrylic Nails Thetford, Contact information map and directions contact form opening hours services ratings photos videos and announcements from Nails by natasha Jane Makeup artist Thetford.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 Best Best hairstyle for big round face male for Natural Beauty</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/best-hairstyle-for-big-round-face-male/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 04:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/best-hairstyle-for-big-round-face-male/</guid>
      <description>Best Hairstyle For Big Round Face Male, Any men will get a super look with this kind of style for a round face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>13 Awesome What hair color suits me upload photo for Trend 2021</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/what-hair-color-suits-me-upload-photo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 21:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/what-hair-color-suits-me-upload-photo/</guid>
      <description>What Hair Color Suits Me Upload Photo, It can be an extremely difficult decision to change something that can. Although there are some people that dont think twice about changing up their hair color there are others that are far more hesitant to alter their natural locks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Cute Acrylic nails ombre matte for Trend 2021</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/acrylic-nails-ombre-matte/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 20:49:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/acrylic-nails-ombre-matte/</guid>
      <description>Acrylic Nails Ombre Matte, Add up an accent finger to the perfectly matte shade and this can offer you a perfect look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>26 Cute Fingers burning after acrylic nails for Natural Beauty</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/fingers-burning-after-acrylic-nails/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 19:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/fingers-burning-after-acrylic-nails/</guid>
      <description>Fingers Burning After Acrylic Nails, There are three main issues that can arise when youre using. But it can turn negative when getting your nails done causes an allergic reaction or irritation that may even affect more than the skin around your fingers says a Baylor College of Medicine expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>28 Best Taking out contact lenses with acrylic nails for Trend 2021</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/taking-out-contact-lenses-with-acrylic-nails/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 15:53:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/taking-out-contact-lenses-with-acrylic-nails/</guid>
      <description>Taking Out Contact Lenses With Acrylic Nails, And in some cases they might even cause damage if they are used incorrectly either with a bad procedure or too many applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>24 Best Whats the difference between acrylic and shellac nails for Natural Beauty</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/whats-the-difference-between-acrylic-and-shellac-nails/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 15:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/whats-the-difference-between-acrylic-and-shellac-nails/</guid>
      <description>Whats The Difference Between Acrylic And Shellac Nails, Like acrylic nails shellac nails cannot be used to extend the nails. Shellac works best if you want the most natural finish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>24 Beautiful Does bob hair suit round faces for Natural Beauty</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/does-bob-hair-suit-round-faces/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 14:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/does-bob-hair-suit-round-faces/</guid>
      <description>Does Bob Hair Suit Round Faces, Given this ones chubby and round face can be easily covered in the forehead and the entire facial structure gets to look oval instead of round.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>23 Top What hairstyles suit chubby faces for Trend 2022</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/what-hairstyles-suit-chubby-faces/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 14:20:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/what-hairstyles-suit-chubby-faces/</guid>
      <description>What Hairstyles Suit Chubby Faces, You can even try this kind of pixie haircut for chubby faces. What kinds of hairstyles suit people with chubby faces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Top How much is it to get acrylic nails done for Trend 2022</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/how-much-is-it-to-get-acrylic-nails-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 13:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/how-much-is-it-to-get-acrylic-nails-done/</guid>
      <description>How Much Is It To Get Acrylic Nails Done, When they remove your acrylics for this price at salons they will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>28 Top Acrylic nail designs fall 2019 </title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/acrylic-nail-designs-fall-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 13:09:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/acrylic-nail-designs-fall-2019/</guid>
      <description>Acrylic Nail Designs Fall 2019, Sep 7 2019 - Explore angel dereks board nails on Pinterest. Fall Nail Designs Autumn Nail Arts autumnfall nails are just as versatile as other seasons give these cute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>21 Great Acrylic nail tools suppliers for Natural Beauty</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/acrylic-nail-tools-suppliers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/acrylic-nail-tools-suppliers/</guid>
      <description>Acrylic Nail Tools Suppliers, From 17 00 from. From 18 00 from. Close esc Quick shop.
Cute And Cool Nail Art Designs Ideas Nail Supplies Nail Supply Store Nail Art Supplies Acrylic Nail Supplies From br.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>25 Great How to get sharpie off acrylic nails for Trend 2021</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/how-to-get-sharpie-off-acrylic-nails/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 09:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/how-to-get-sharpie-off-acrylic-nails/</guid>
      <description>How To Get Sharpie Off Acrylic Nails, Qualified Orders Over 35 Ship Free. Immediately wrap your nail and the cotton ball in aluminum foil to hold the cotton to your nail and also to keep the acetone from evaporating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>32 Great Acrylic nail ideas winter for Trend 2022</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/acrylic-nail-ideas-winter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 09:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/acrylic-nail-ideas-winter/</guid>
      <description>Acrylic Nail Ideas Winter, Keep Your Hands Moisturized. Dec 1 2015 - Explore Katie Carsons board winter acrylic nails followed by 188 people on Pinterest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>21 Cute How to add fringe to a knitted scarf </title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/how-to-add-fringe-to-a-knitted-scarf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 09:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/how-to-add-fringe-to-a-knitted-scarf/</guid>
      <description>How To Add Fringe To A Knitted Scarf, When cold weather hits a warm scarf is essential. The Just For Him Classic Ribbed Scarf Patterncan be made to any size just chain the number of chains you need to reach the length you want for your scarf and then begin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>25 Cute Cute acrylic nails for 10 year olds </title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/cute-acrylic-nails-for-10-year-olds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 07:18:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/cute-acrylic-nails-for-10-year-olds/</guid>
      <description>Cute Acrylic Nails For 10 Year Olds, Am going to let her have a manipedi and get her real nails painted with the bridal party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>28  What is southeast asian skin tone for Trend 2022</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/what-is-southeast-asian-skin-tone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 06:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/what-is-southeast-asian-skin-tone/</guid>
      <description>What Is Southeast Asian Skin Tone, That is why many Korean women pay for a color matching service called the personal color diagnosis in which a colorist uses a machine called Cube to first detect the exact level of brightness yellowness and redness of your skin tone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>19 Beautiful Do round faces look better with long or short hair for Trend 2022</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/do-round-faces-look-better-with-long-or-short-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 05:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/do-round-faces-look-better-with-long-or-short-hair/</guid>
      <description>Do Round Faces Look Better With Long Or Short Hair, The most flattering hairstyles for those with round faces is a center part with long pieces or long layers around the face if you want to narrow out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Top What is the best hair length for a square face for Natural Beauty</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/what-is-the-best-hair-length-for-a-square-face/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 04:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/what-is-the-best-hair-length-for-a-square-face/</guid>
      <description>What Is The Best Hair Length For A Square Face, Layering this hair length can be tricky but not impossible. Thus the main rule for square-shaped faces is to avoid anything too wide that isnt also tall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>32 Top What happens if you dont style curtain bangs for Natural Beauty</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/what-happens-if-you-dont-style-curtain-bangs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 03:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/what-happens-if-you-dont-style-curtain-bangs/</guid>
      <description>What Happens If You Dont Style Curtain Bangs, Theyre often long and have soft wispy ends that give off a laidback vibe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>24 Awesome How to know if your face suits short hair for Trend 2021</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/how-to-know-if-your-face-suits-short-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 02:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/how-to-know-if-your-face-suits-short-hair/</guid>
      <description>How To Know If Your Face Suits Short Hair, Haircut For Diamond Faces. Maybe it adds width on the sides or draws attention away from a pointier chin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>13 Cute Coffin acrylic nails for fall for Trend 2021</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/coffin-acrylic-nails-for-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 22:49:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/coffin-acrylic-nails-for-fall/</guid>
      <description>Coffin Acrylic Nails For Fall, Nails of this shape are thinner at the sides and broader at the bottom suitable for long and very versatile nails suitable for many different surfaces and lacquer designs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>27 Cute How to soften my natural hair at home for Natural Beauty</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/how-to-soften-my-natural-hair-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 22:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/how-to-soften-my-natural-hair-at-home/</guid>
      <description>How To Soften My Natural Hair At Home, Scalding water steals away the natural moisturizing oils from the hair. Then I added a few spoons of honey two tea spoons of apple cider vinegar one table spoonful of mayonnaise because it contains eggs and vegetable oils and two spoonfuls of my Henna deep conditioner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>27  Will i suit curtain bangs for Natural Beauty</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/will-i-suit-curtain-bangs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 21:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/will-i-suit-curtain-bangs/</guid>
      <description>Will I Suit Curtain Bangs, Another beautiful style that works on different face shapes is the side-swept bang. To make this style look even more appealing you can have a center part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>23 Best Best haircut for round face shape male for Trend 2021</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/best-haircut-for-round-face-shape-male/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 19:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/best-haircut-for-round-face-shape-male/</guid>
      <description>Best Haircut For Round Face Shape Male, Tight curly hair. 8 best Male Celebrity Facial Shapes images on Pinterest. One of the most popular mens haircuts for round faces has to be the classic pompadour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>24 Great Which is the most powerful character in free fire for Trend 2021</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/which-is-the-most-powerful-character-in-free-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 18:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/which-is-the-most-powerful-character-in-free-fire/</guid>
      <description>Which Is The Most Powerful Character In Free Fire, However what sets Free Fire apart from the rest is its character system which adds lots of variety to the game and allows players to unlock new.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>22 Cute Short hairstyle for chubby face 2021 for Trend 2022</title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/short-hairstyle-for-chubby-face-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 13:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/short-hairstyle-for-chubby-face-2021/</guid>
      <description>Short Hairstyle For Chubby Face 2021, A short bob haircut also gives a fantastic appearance to your chubby face. You can get many ideas pictures videos and suggestions of Short Hairstyles for Fat Faces and Double Chins 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>29 Beautiful How to take off salon acrylic nails </title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/how-to-take-off-salon-acrylic-nails/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 11:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/how-to-take-off-salon-acrylic-nails/</guid>
      <description>How To Take Off Salon Acrylic Nails, For gel polish and acrylic nails let it sit for at least 20 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Top Brown nail after acrylics </title>
      <link>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/brown-nail-after-acrylics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 08:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairpict.github.io/hair-nail/brown-nail-after-acrylics/</guid>
      <description>Brown Nail After Acrylics, However if curing is overdone or the opposite underdone meaning you left your nails under the lamp for too short the material can start turning brown after a few days or a week later.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>